#大家好 今天來攝影小哥家蹭飯吃哦 順便帶一點青菜
Hi everyone! Today I'll have a meal at Mr. Cameraman's place. I have brought some vegetables with me
#來 餵兔子 兔子在那樓上
to, to feed the bunnies. The bunnies are upstairs.
#好久沒有看過它啦 上去看一下
I haven't seen them for a long time. Get's go!
#小兔兔
Little bunnies!
#你看天氣熱 它們都霍霍霍霍霍的 你看 都是
See? It's hot and they are all like "ho ho ho ho ho". See? All are
#呼吸加速
breathing rapidly.
#它前兩 呃 前天 前天跑到外面去
Several, two days, two day ago, it ran away,
#搞到一身都是黃泥
so it is now covered with dirt.
#被攝影小哥被逮回來啦
Mr. Cameraman captured it and took it back.
#來 給你們吃一點
Come on! This is for you.
#好吃的
It's tasty!
#我特意從鄉下帶過來的哦
I brought it all the way from my village.
#你看 你看 不老實
See? See? It is so naughty!
#一打開籠子你想要出去
It wants to go outside once the cage is opened.
#外面的世界不合適你呀
The world outside is not for you.
#很嫩的哦
It's crispy and juicy,
#是不是很嫩
isn't it?
#新鮮的蔬菜 要不要出來哦
It's fresh vegetables. Do you want to come out?
#一想到外面 它就想出來
It wants to run away whenever it thinks about the world outside.
#出來 看一下你
Come out! Let me have a look!
#你看 這麼髒啊 我都不好意思給它洗澡
See? It's so dirty that I don't even want to wash it.
#來 吃點
Come on! Eat!
#菜葉子
Vegetables
#很好吃的
It's tasty!
#這個差不多四斤多哦 你看 那麼大了
This one is almost 2kg. See? It's so big now.
#你看 好聽話啊 它
See? What a good bunny.
#嗯 耳朵
Um! Ears.
#蹲在這裡不敢動
It's staying there and doesn't even dare to move.
#是不是 我好久沒來看你了 是不是
Right? We haven't met for a long time, right?
#你看你的耳朵都那麼大了
You see? Your ears are very big now.
#有沒有想我啊
Do you miss me?
#耳朵好大啊 這個耳朵
The ears are very big, the ears.
#你看 那麼老實
See? It is a good bunny.
#一動不動的哦 蹲在這個角落里面
It is just staying at the corner, and is not moving at all.
#這樣才乖 知不知道
This is good, you know?
#我們都是好朋友來的
We are good friends.
#不能這樣 不能冷落我哦
Come on! You can't be so indifferent to me.
#不能冷落我哦 要熱情一點
Don't be so indifferent to me! Show me your passion!
#不然我帶你去河邊玩哦
Otherwise I'll have some fun with you on the riverside.
#你看
See?
#一動不動的這個
It is not moving at all.
#出來啊 要不要出來
Come! Do you want to come out?
#要不要出來
Do you?
#不肯出來
It doesn't want to.
#那麼壞
Naughty!
#不想出來你就吃這個啊
Eat it if you don't wanna come out!
#這個你又不吃
You don't eat it neither.
#別發脾氣哦
Mind your temper!
#你看它
See?
#肯定不歡迎我了
It doesn't welcome me.
#這個樣子
Look at its face!
#縐著眉頭來看我
It frowns upon me.
#又沒對你做甚麼
I didn't even do anything to you.
#你怎麼這樣子
Why?
#要不要去洗澡 趕緊洗一下這裡
Let's go to have a bath. Let's wash here.
#那麼髒
It's so dirty.
#去不去
Are you going?
#去就把手伸過來
Give me you hand if you are going!
#走啊
Let's go!
#好啦 今天的視頻到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.
#有空的時候我帶你們去洗一下澡
When I have the time I will wash you,
一個一個洗
all three of you,
一次洗三個
one by one.
走啦 走啦
Go go go!